http://www.meet-the-one.com/privacy_policy.php

---
45464748495051525354555657585960616263646566676869707172737475767778798081828384858687888990919293949596979899
---
45464748495051525354555657585960616263646566676869707172737475767778798081828384858687888990919293949596979899
From
ArgentinaAustraliaAustriaBelarusBelgiumBosnia and HerzegovinaBrazilBulgariaCanadaChileColombiaCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCzech RepublicDenmarkDominican RepublicEcuadorEstoniaFinlandFranceGermanyGreeceGuatemalaHungaryIcelandIrelandIsraelItalyJamaicaLatviaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMexicoMonacoNetherlandsNew ZealandNicaraguaNorwayPanamaParaguayPeruPolandPortugalRomaniaRussiaSerbiaSlovakiaSloveniaSouth AfricaSpainSwedenSwitzerlandUnited KingdomUnited StatesThailandTurkeyUkraineUruguayVenezuela
Search
Privacy Policy
1 General information
1.1 50plus-Club attaches a great deal of importance to ensuring that its users data is secure and protected. 50plus-Club undertakes to observe the legal provisions on data protection, particularly the German Data Protection Act (BDSG) and the German Teleservices Act (TMG).
1.2 The User is hereby informed pursuant to Section 33, Para. 1, of the German Data Protection Act and Section 5 of the German Teleservices Act that 50plus-Club shall save and automatically process the User's data in a machine-readable format.
1.3 Personal data is collected, saved, processed and used within the context of rendering the contractual services. Personal data is data which contains information about the personal and factual circumstances of an identified or identifiable user. Data is saved electronically. All data queried and entered as a profile is saved. When a profile is deleted, all of the data that enables the User to be identified shall be deleted.
1.4 50plus-Club shall provide the User with full and free information about the data it has saved provided that said data does actually concern the User. This information shall be provided in writing. The User shall make any requests for information in writing, enclosing a copy of their identity card, and send the same to 50plus-Treff GmbH, Schloﬂbergstr. 24, 82319 Starnberg. In this regard, 50plus-Club would like to inform the User that it only requires their name, address, date of birth and validity period to identify the User by means of a copy of their identity card. The User should therefore black out all other data on the copy of their identity card (e.g. identity card number, photo, personal features, nationality). 50plus-Club uses the copy of the identity card only to verify the User's identity, after which it destroys it.
1.5 All of the User's data and their profile, which is also visible on 50plus-Club to other users, including their pseudonym, interests, description, photo, age, post code, etc., can be passed on to other registered users of 50plus-Club to expand the potential audience for their profile. The User's pseudonym, but not their identity (email address), is disclosed.
1.6 In addition, 50plus-Club does not disclose any individual personal data to third parties. Publication of the profile is one exception, as the User entered their data for the purpose of creating said profile and consented to disclosure of said data upon registration.
1.7 The personal settings that the User makes shall be stored. This ensures that the User finds their personal settings again at the start of each new session (each time they log in). 50plus-Club normally uses cookies for this purpose. The User's browser permanently saves these cookies on the User's hard drive. The User can make appropriate settings in their browser to prevent this from happening.
1.8 If the User accesses the 50plus-Club services via a partner website (affiliate), the anonymised data shall be stored in a cookie. These cookies do not contain any of the User's personal data, but serve only to maintain the partner program. These cookies are automatically deleted when the User registers. If the User does not register, these cookies are automatically deleted after 30 days.
1.9 The User receives email newsletters. This correspondence forms part of the service, informs the User of current topics and news relating to 50plus-Club and contains member-specific messages (e.g. through correspondence from other users, profile visits). At all times, the User is free to decide whether they would like to stop the email newsletter part of the service, whether entirely or only for a certain period of time, to unsubscribe from the service using the link provided at the end of the relevant newsletter or to re-subscribe to the service using the various settings in their account.
1.10 In registering, the User declares that they consent to their data being used in the matter described in the above provisions.
1.11 Our website can generally be used without the need to provide personal data. When 50plus-Club has collected personal data (e.g. name, address or email addresses) on its website, it is ensured that the User has provided said data on a voluntary basis, where possible.
1.12 Within the context of the statutory provisions, 50plus-Club may evaluate user profiles using a pseudonym for the purposes of advertising, market research and improving its services. The User may object to user profiles such as these being created at any time, e.g. by emailing info@50plus-club.com. These user profiles are not associated with data via the user of the pseudonym.
1.13 The User's IP address is required to transmit data when calling up the pages of our website. In addition, 50plus-Club only collects the User's IP address, e.g. for statistical purposes, in an anonymised state and does not associate it with other data. This means that it is impossible to trace it back to an individual person.
50plus-Club would like to point out that that there may be security loopholes when transferring data online (e.g. when communicating by email). Information cannot be fully protected against access by third parties.
50plus-Club hereby expressly objects to third parties using the contact details published within the context of the legal notice requirements in order to send unsolicited advertising and information. 50plus-Club expressly reserves the right to take legal action should advertising information be sent unsolicited, e.g. by means of spam emails.
2 Data privacy declaration for using Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses so-called "cookies", which are text files saved on your computer to help the website analyse how visitors use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website will generally be transmitted to and stored on a server run by Google in the United States.
If IP anonymisation is activated on this website, however, Google will truncate your IP address in advance within European Union member states or within other states that are parties to the European Economic Area Agreement. Only in exceptional cases is the full IP address transmitted to and truncated on one of Google's servers in the United States. On behalf of the website administrator, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, for the purpose of compiling reports on the website activities and rendering services to the website administrator with respect to website and Internet usage.
The IP address transmitted by your browser within the context of Google Analytics will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You may prevent the storage of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use all of the functions of this website. You can also prevent the data generated by the cookie with respect to your website usage (including your IP address) from being recorded and processed by Google by simply downloading and installing the browser plugin available at the following link: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en
You will find more detailed information about usage conditions and data privacy at http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html and at http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/learn/privacy.html. We would like to point out that Google Analytics has been expanded to include the "gat._anonymizeIp();" code, so as to guarantee anonymised collection of IP addresses (so-called IP masking).
3 Data privacy declaration for using Google AdSense
This website uses Google AdSense, a web advertising service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google AdSense uses so-called "cookies", which are text files saved on your computer to help the website analyse how visitors use the site. Google AdSense also uses so-called "web beacons" (invisible graphics). Information such as user traffic on this website can be evaluated through the use of these web beacons.
The information generated by cookies and web beacons about your use of the website (including your IP address) and the delivery of advertising formats will be transmitted to and stored on a server run by Google in the United States. Google may transfer this information to its contractual partners. However, Google will not associate your IP address with any other data saved by Google.
You may prevent the installation of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use all of the functions of this website. You can prevent Google from displaying any interest-based advertising whatsoever by clicking on the "Deactivate" button at the following link http://www.google.com/settings/ads and by making other related settings. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
15 Members online
f 50 - Carerra
f 52 - Caylar
f 56 - Mimi2121
f 56 - Nelly01
f 64 - Yayita
f 70 - Evergreen50
m 60 - kehall
m 64 - sweesteve...
m 49 - Doktorhol...
m 45 - Couldxuse...
f 65 - K2butterf...
m 45 - KennedyGe...
f 62 - Butterfly...
m 60 - Peifo.
Our site uses cookies. By continuing to browse this site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies. Find out more †††OK
